Justin Mao

<u>jmao.co</u> <u>github.com/justinmao</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/justinmao</u> justin@jmao.co 2307-5 St Joseph Street Toronto ON M4Y0B6 Canada (647) 949-1565

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Summer internship experience in software development at Nissan Motors
Freelance development/design work building an online platform for a hybrid/online fitness startup
Strong design skills developed as Creative & Media Director of Jane Goodall's Institute's Roots & Shoots:
University of Toronto Chapter
Volunteer work through Habitat for Humanity International in Sri Lanka and Indonesia

Bilingual in English and Mandarin Chinese

US citizen

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES6), React.js, Express, Node.js, jQuery HTML/CSS, Sass
Python, SciPy/NumPy, pandas, TensorFlow
Java, Spring
SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Intern

Jun 2017 – Aug 2017 (3 Months) Guangzhou, China

Nissan Motors

JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS

Java, Spring, MySQL, Oracle

- Led the design and implementation of a component used by the Passenger Vehicle (PV) department to display WeChat/SMS promotional campaign information as well as statistics regarding their usage
- Automated data validation and resumption of corrupted or interrupted client data processes
- Created a tool for automatic generation of Excel spreadsheet summary reports
- Contributed to and debugged various data processing systems and visualization components

Freelance Web Developer/Designer

Nov 2017 – Present (Ongoing)

NOSUCHTHING training (nosuchthing.training)

Toronto, Canada

JavaScript, React.js, Sass, HTML

Express, Node.js, WordPress (Headless)

- Designed and developed a web platform for the client to build an online presence/brand identity
- Integrated with existing SaaS components used by the client
- Provided server setup, administration, and maintenance
- Periodically collaborated with the client to iteratively improve features and UI/UX

EDUCATION

Honours Bachelor of Science (HBSc), Specialist in Computer Science University of Toronto

Sep 2014 – Jun 2018